<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GhostHunters_CS2110 2.0</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_screen">GameScreen</string>
    <string name="howToPlay">Touch the screen to charge up the ball. Ghosts will advance towards the
        ball when it is charging. Avoid ghosts; if they hit the ball, it loses health. When the ball
        reaches 0 health, it dies and the game is over. When the ball is charged up, run into ghosts
        to kill them. Ghosts will not advance towards you if you touch the screen while you are
        charged up. Various items will spawn while you are playing. These items can help you
        in various ways. Click the items button below to explore the various items there are.</string>
    <string name="easyName">Difficulty: Easy</string>
    <string name="mediumName">Difficulty: Medium</string>
    <string name="hardName">Difficulty: Hard</string>
    <string name="easyDesc">In Easy mode, you start with a Friendly Ghost, the ray gun has no
    cooldown on shots per second, ghosts do normal damage, and charge runs out slowly.</string>
    <string name="mediumDesc">In Medium mode, you do not start with a Friendly Ghost. Instead, you
    must earn at least 400 points. A new one appears at every 1000 points after that first 400.
    Ghosts do normal damage, the ray gun has a slight cooldown on how many rays can be shot per
    second, and charge runs out at a normal rate.</string>
    <string name="hardDesc">In Hard mode, you do not start with a Friendly Ghost. Instead, you must
    earn at least 800 points on your own. A new one appears at every 1000 points after that first
    800. In addition, ghosts do double damage, the ray gun has a long cooldown on how many rays can be
    shot per second, and charge runs out quickly. Also, ghosts do not stop when you stop touching
    the screen, and will continue in a straight line until stopped by continuous bounces.</string>
    <string name="extraHealthName">Health Pack</string>
    <string name="fearName">Ghost Repellent</string>
    <string name="rayGunName">Ray Gun</string>
    <string name="shieldName">Shield</string>
    <string name="timeFreezerName">Ghost Freezer</string>
    <string name="extraHealthDesc">Restores some lost health to the ball.</string>
    <string name="fearDesc">The ghosts become scared of the ball for a short time, causing them to
    run away from the ball when the screen is touched rather than towards it.</string>
    <string name="rayGunDesc">The ball equips a ray gun, giving it the ability to shoot rays with
    every touch of the screen. These rays pierce ghosts, rewarding 100 points for each ghost killed.</string>
    <string name="shieldDesc">The ball equips a shield, protecting it from the damage of one ghost.
    If a ghost is killed while wearing a shield, 100 points are awarded.</string>
    <string name="timeFreezerDesc">The ghosts become frozen for a time, preventing them from directing
    their movement. However, on hard difficulty, the ghosts continue to move; they simply stop
    tracking the ball on touch. </string>
</resources>
